Guide to the Walter Isard papers, 1938-1986.
Isard, Walter papers
- Correspondence 1951-1953 A, 1951-1953 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  A
- Atomic Power by Isard and Whitney, 1951-1952 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, 1951-1953 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  B-Z
- Correspondence, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1954-1956 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- August 19, 1953; To Regional Researchers; Robock and Ruttan paper, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Isard-Neff, Regional Committee Corresp., 1950-1951, 1950-1951 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Replies to Neff-Isard Letter, Summer 1950, 1950 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Jan 1951, Re. Christmas meeting-Dec. 29,1950, 1951 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Letter to Herring--Proposed Objectives of Committee, Jan. 9, 1951, 1951 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  Letter to SSRC on Regional Economic Studies committee
- Jan 9, 1951-Re. Economic Research Meeting Chicago, Dec. 29, 1950, 1951 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Feb. 20, 1951-Re. Herring Rejection, 1951 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  SSRC rejection for committee
- April 21, 1951- To Regional Researchers: Re. Milwaukee meeting, April 20,1951, 1951 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- May 1,1951- To Regional Researchers: Re. May Mtg., 1951 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- May 31, 1951-To Regional Researchers: May Mtg. Report; Vining Paper Outline, 1951 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- July 11, 1951- Memo to Regional & Urban Sociologists, Human Ecologists-Re. Mtg. Sept. 6, 1951, 1951 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Memorandum to Regional Researchers- July 25, 1951 (by WI), 1951 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- August 13, 1951- To Regional Sociologists, 1951 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Interdisciplinary Mtg., Regional Sociologists, Sept 1951--Letters, 1951 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Notes--So. Econ. Assoc. Mtgs., University Program--Nov. 16, 1951, 1951 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Correspondence--Harvard Interdisciplinary Session March 1952 and Follow-up July 1952, 1952 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Aug. 19, 1952- To Regional Researchers Re. Aug 7th mtg. (AAG Convention) + other correspondence re. mtg, 1952 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Sept. 3-5, 1952- American Sociological Society 47th Annual Mtg. (Correspondence), 1952 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Sept 10, 1953- Interdisciplinary Regional Session and APSA conference, Hotel Statler, D.C., 1953 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Sept 1953- American Political Science Association meeting-correspondence, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Correspondence Re. Dec. 1953 Econometric Society Meetings (Regional Sessions), 1953 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Dec. 1953 AEA mtgs (Regional Sessions) Correspondence, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  American Economic Association sessions
- A.A.A.S. Dec. 1953, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  American Association for the Advancement of Science
- Jan. 7, 8, 9, 1954- Columbia University Bicentennial- "The Metropolis in Modern Life", 1954 (Box 14, Folder 25)
- 1954 April, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  Correspondence (American Association of Geographers/AAG)
- August 3, 1954- To Regional Researchers, Re. Formation of an Association, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 27)
- Nov. 10, 1954- To Regional Scientists, Re. Dec. Mtg. in Detroit, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 28)
- Sept. 30, 1954- To Regional Researchers, Re. December Mtgs., 1954 (Box 14, Folder 29)
- Dec. 9, 1953- To Regional Researchers + Notes on Mtg. with Political Scientists Sept 1953, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 30)
- March 8. 1954- To Regional Researchers, Re. AAG Mtgs., 1954 (Box 14, Folder 31)
- Dec. 12, 1952- To Regional Researchers, Re. Christmas mtgs. + "Human Geography and Area Research" Edward Ullman, 1952 (Box 14, Folder 32)
- Oct. 23, 1952- To Regional Researchers, 1952 (Box 14, Folder 33)
- July 1952- To Regional Researchers, Re. Preston James Rept., 1952 (Box 14, Folder 34)
- April 11,1952- To Regional Researchers, Re. April 25 mtg., 1952 (Box 14, Folder 35)
- Jan. 25, 1952- To Regional Researchers, Re. Upcoming Mtgs., 1952 (Box 14, Folder 36)
- Proceedings of Christmas Meeting, 1951 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  Regional Economic Research Meeting
- Correspondence Lists 1950-1951, 1950-1951 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  A.A.G. 1951 list of participants
- A 1953-1954, 1953-1954 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- APSA, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- AWR 1953-1954, 1953-1954 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- B 1953- 1954, 1952-1954 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Philadelphia City Planning Commission, MIT, Edmund Bacon Corresp., 1953-1954 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Bemis conference; Bacon Corresp. Re. City of Phila. Planning Commission 1953-1954, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- C (+Phila. Chamber of Commerce) 1953-4, 1953-1954 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- D 1953-4, 1952-1954 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- E 1953-4, 1953-1954 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- F 1953-4, 1953-1954 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- G 1953-4, 1952-1954 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- H 1953-4, 1952-1954 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- I-J 1953-1954, 1953-1954 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- K 1953-4, 1953-1954 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- L (+Robert Lindsay Corresp.) 1953-4, 1953-1954 (Box 15, Folder 15a)
- Robert Lindsay Correspondence, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 15b)
- M 1953-4, 1953-1954 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- MIT- miscellaneous and official 1953-4, 1953-1954 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Miscellaneous 1953-4, 1953-1954 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- N 1953-4, 1953-1954 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- O 1953-4, 1953-1954 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- P 1953-4, 1953-1954 (Box 15, Folder 21a)
- Printing and Publishing, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 21b)
- Prospective Students 1954, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 21c)
- Puerto Rico- Chronological, 1953-1954 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Regional Plan Association 1953-4, 1953-1954 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- R 1953-4, 1953-1954 (Box 15, Folder 24)
- S 1953-4, 1951-1954 (Box 15, Folder 25)
- T 1953-4, 1953-1954 (Box 15, Folder 26)
- U-V 1953-4, 1953-4 (Box 15, Folder 27)
- W 1953-4, 1952-1954 (Box 15, Folder 28)
- Z 1953-4, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 29)
- A 1956-60, 1956-1958 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- B 1956-60, 1956-1960 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- C 1956-60, 1956-1960 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- D 1956-60, 1956-1960 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- E 1956-60, 1956-1960 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- F 1956-60, 1956-1960 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- G 1956-60, 1956-1960 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- H 1956-60, 1956-1960 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- I-J 1956-1960, 1956-1960 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- K 1956-60, 1956-1960 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- L 1956-1960, 1956-1960 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- M 1956-1960, 1956-1960 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- N 1956-1960, 1956-1960 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- O 1956-1960, 1956-1960 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- P 1956-1960, 1956-1960 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- R 1956-1960, 1956-1960 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- S 1956-1960, 1956-1960 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- T 1956-1960, 1956-1960 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- U-V 1956-1960, 1956-1960 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- W (a) 1956-1960, 1956-1960 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- W (b) 1956-1960, 1956-1960 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- X Y Z 1956-1960, 1956-1960 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- RSA Corresp.--Atlanta 1973, A-P, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- RSA Corresp.--Atlanta 1973, P-Z, 1972-1973 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- RSA Corresp.--Vienna conference 1973, A-L, 1972-1974 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- RSA Corresp.--Vienna conference 1973, L-Z some K, 1972-1973 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- PSSI Corresp./program- Geneva 1974, 1973-1974 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- RSA Karlsruhe 1974 A-S, 1973-1974 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- RSA Karlsruhe 1974, S-Z + Programs, 1973-1974 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- PSSI--Chicago 1974, Program/Corresp., 1974 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- PRS (I)--Zurich 1975 Conference, A-L, 1973-1975 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- PRS (I) Misc. corresp., 1973-1975 (Box 17, Folder 10a)
- PRS (I)-- 1975 Zurich, Conference and Program, L-Z, 1973-1975 (Box 17, Folder 10b)
- RSA Cambridge 1975, A-L, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- RSA Cambridge, MA--1975, L-Z, 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- RSA Budapest 1975, A-K, 1973-1975 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- RSA Budapest K-R, 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- RSA Budapest 1975, S-Z, 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- PSS (I) Cambridge, MA 1975 and Ann Arbor 1976--Corrresp. A-H, 1974-1976 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- PSS (I) Cambridge 1975 and Ann Arbor 1976 (both together), H-Z, 1974-1976 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- PSS (I) Geneva 1976 Corresp. A-O, 1975-1976 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- PSSI Geneva 1976 Corresp. O-Z, 1975-1976 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- RSA Copenhagen Conference 1976 A- K, 1974-1976 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- RSA Copenhagen Conference 1976 K-Z, program, 1974-1976 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- Peace Research Society - Volume 2, 1968-1972 (Box 17, Folder 22)
- PSSI Ghent 1964 Program, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- PRSI 1965 Warsaw, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- PSSI Newsletters & Correspondence, 1970-1979 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- PSSI Cambridge 1967, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- PRS(I) Budapest 1968, Correspondence A - L, 1967-1968 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- PRS(I) Budapest 1968, Correspondence L - Z, 1967-1968 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- PRSI Vietnam Conference, June 1968, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- PRSI Conference-Cambridge, MA 1968, Corresp. A - H, 1967-1968 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- PRSI Conference 1968 Cambridge, MA--Vietnam, Corresp. H-Z, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- PRSI Copenhagen 1969, A - N, 1968-1969 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- PRSI Copenhagen 1969, Corresp. N-Z, 1966-1969 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- PRSI Michigan Union. 1969, 1968-1969 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Early Bird Session RSA, 1968 Cambridge, MA, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- RSA Budapest Conference Corresp. 1968, A- K, 1967-1968 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- RSA 1968 Budapest Conference Correspondence K-Z, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- RSA 1968 Cambridge, MA correspondence A-L, 1967-1968 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- RSA 1968 Cambridge MA correspondence L-Z, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- RSA Poona 1969, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 18)
- RSA Western-Far Eastern conference in Hawaii, Sept.1968, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 19)
- RSA conference 1969 London, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 20)
- RSA Santa Monica 1969, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 21)
- PRSI Rome 1970, corresp. A-J, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 22)
- PRSI Rome 1970, corresp. J-Z, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 23)
- RSA Conference Copenhagen 1969 A-K, 1968-1969 (Box 18, Folder 24)
- RSA Conference Copenhagen 1969 K-Z, 1968-1969 (Box 18, Folder 25)
- RSA London 1970 A- L, 1969-1970 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- RSA London 1970 L-Z, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Philadelphia RSA 1970, A - M, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Philadelphia RSA 1970, M - Z, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- RSA- Ann Arbor 1971, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- PSSI- Philadelphia 1970, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- PSSI-- Ann Arbor 1971, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- RSA Philadelphia 1972, A - M, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- RSA Philadelphia 1971, M - Z, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- PSS(I) 1972 Rotterdam, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- PSS(I) Philadelphia 1972, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- RSA Rotterdam 1972, A - N, 1971-1972 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- RSA Rotterdam 1972, N-Z, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- PSS(I) Conference 1973, Cambridge, MA (program, correspondence), 1973 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- PSSI Vienna A-K 1973, 1972-1973 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- PSSI Vienna 1973, K - Z Corresp., 1973 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Rehovot (Israel) Conference on Urbanization & Development, Aug. 1971, 1970-1971 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- AEA Toronto 1971, 1971-1972 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- RSA Midwest Continental Section 1972, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Multi-Lingual Section RSA 1972, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Western Section, RSA 1972, 1972-1975 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- RSA Karlsruhe 1972, RSI Institute, 1972-1974 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- RSA Karlsruhe RS Institute 1973-74, 1972-1976 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Stockholm RS Conference 1973, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- RSA Cambridge MA- 1975, Ph.D.Correspondence, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- PSSI Middle East Conference, Cambridge MA 1970, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- PSSI London 1971, A-R, 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- PSSI London 1971, R-Z, 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- RSA Rome 1971, 1st File A -G, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- RSA Rome 1971, 1st File G-Z, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- RSA Ann Arbor 1971, A- M, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- RSA Ann Arbor 1971, A-M, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- RSA British Section, Aug 1972, 1971-1972 (Box 20, Folder 16)
- Corresp. 1966-73 A, 1966-1973 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Corresp. 1966-73 B, 1966-1973 (Box 20, Folder 18)
- Corresp. 1966-73 Cl, 1966-1973 (Box 20, Folder 19)
- Corresp. 1966-73 CZ, 1966-1973 (Box 20, Folder 20)
- Corresp. 1966-73 D, 1966-1973 (Box 20, Folder 21)
- Corresp. 1966-73 E, 1966-1973 (Box 20, Folder 22)
- Corresp. 1966-73 F, 1966-1973 (Box 20, Folder 23)
- Corresp. 1966-73 G, 1966-1973 (Box 20, Folder 24)
- Corresp. 1966-73 H, 1966-1973 (Box 20, Folder 25)
- Corresp. 1966-73 I - J, 1966-1973 (Box 20, Folder 26)
- Corresp. 1966-73 K, 1966-1973 (Box 20, Folder 27)
- Corresp. 1966-73 L, 1966-1973 (Box 20, Folder 28)
- Corresp. 1966-73 M1, 1966-1973 (Box 20, Folder 29)
- Corresp. 1966-73 M2, 1966-1973 (Box 20, Folder 30)
- Corresp. 1965-72, A#1, 1965-1972 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Corresp. 1965-72, A#2, 1965-1972 (Box 21, Folder 2a)
- Alrich, 1969-1972 (Box 21, Folder 2b)
- Corresp. 1965-1972, B, 1965-1972 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Corresp. 1965-1972, B#2, 1965-1972 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Corresp. 1965-1972, B#3, 1965-1972 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Corresp. 1965-1972, B#4, 1965-1972 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Corresp. 1965-1972, B#5, 1965-1972 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Corresp. 1965-1972, B#6, 1965-1972 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Corresp. 1965-1972, C#1, 1965-1972 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Corresp. 1965-1972, C#2, 1965-1972 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Corresp. 1965-1972, C#3, 1965-1972 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Corresp. 1965-1972, C#4, 1965-1972 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Corresp. 1965-1972, C#5, 1965-1972 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Corresp. 1965-1972, D#1, 1965-1972 (Box 21, Folder 14)
- Corresp. 1965-1972, D#2, 1965-1972 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- Corresp. 1965-1972, E, 1965-1972 (Box 21, Folder 16)
- Corresp. 1965-1972, F#1, 1965-1972 (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Corresp. 1965-1972, F#2, 1965-1972 (Box 21, Folder 18)
- Corresp. 1965-1972, G#1, 1965-1972 (Box 21, Folder 19)
- Corresp. 1965-1972, G#2, 1965-1972 (Box 21, Folder 20)
- Corresp. 1965-1972, G#3, 1965-1972 (Box 21, Folder 21)
- N, 1971-1973 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  General correspondence
- O, 1972-1973 (Box 21, Folder 23)
- P, 1972-1973 (Box 21, Folder 24)
- Q-R, 1972-1973 (Box 21, Folder 25)
- S, 1972-1973 (Box 21, Folder 26)
- T, 1972-1973 (Box 21, Folder 27)
- U-V, 1972-1973 (Box 21, Folder 28)
- W, 1972-1973 (Box 21, Folder 29)
- X-Z, 1972-1973 (Box 21, Folder 30)
- Corresp. 1965-72 H1, 1965-1972 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Corresp 1965-72 H2, 1965-1972 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Corresp 1965-72 H3, 1965-1972 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Corresp 1965-72 I, 1965-1972 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Corresp 1965-72 J, 1965-1972 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Corresp 1965-72 K1, 1965-1972 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Corresp 1965-72 K2, 1965-1972 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Corresp 1965-72 L1, 1965-1972 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Corresp 1965-72 L2, 1964-1972 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Corresp 1965-72 L3, 1965-1972 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Corresp 1965-72 M1, 1965-1972 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Corresp 1965-72 M2, 1965-1972 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Corresp 1965-72 M3, 1965-1972 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Corresp 1965-72 M4, 1965-1972 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Corresp 1965-72 N, 1965-1972 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Corresp 1965-72 O, 1965-1972 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Corresp 1965-72 P1, 1965-1972 (Box 22, Folder 17)
- Corresp 1965-72 P2, 1965-1972 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- Corresp 1965-72 R1, 1965-1972 (Box 22, Folder 19)
- Corresp 1965-72 R2, 1965-1972 (Box 22, Folder 20)
- Corresp 1965-72 R3, 1965-1972 (Box 22, Folder 21)
- Corresp 1965-72 R4, 1965-1972 (Box 22, Folder 22)
- RSA 1968, 1967-1968 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Peace Research Society 1964-1967, 1964-1971 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Second Pacific RSA Conference, Sept. 1969, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Miscellaneous, 1964-1967 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  Correspondence on Peace Research and RSA conferences
- 1965-72--S1, 1965-1972 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- 1965-72--S2, 1965-1972 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- 1965-72--S3, 1965-1972 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- 1965-72--S4, 1965-1972 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- 1965-72--S5, 1965-1972 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- 1965-72--S6, 1965-1972 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- 1965-72--T1, 1965-1972 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- 1965-72--T2, 1965-1972 (Box 23, Folder 12)
- 1965-72--Corresp.; Thomas, Morgan, 1964-1972 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- 1965-72 Corresp.; U,V, 1965-1972 (Box 23, Folder 14)
- 1965-72 Corresp.; W1, 1965-1972 (Box 23, Folder 15)
- 1965-72 Corresp.; W2, 1965-1972 (Box 23, Folder 16)
- 1965-72; Corresp.; W3, 1965-1972 (Box 23, Folder 17)
- 1965-72; Corresp.; X, Y, Z, 1965-1972 (Box 23, Folder 18)
- Correspondence-Alperovich, Gershon, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Blair, John E, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Choguill, Charles, 1967-1973 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Choguill, Charles (2), 1967-1972 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Choukroun, JM, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Coraggio, Rosa and Jose, 1967-1973 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Dear, Michael, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Denike, Kenneth, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Desfor, Gene, 1969-1972 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Difiglio, Carmen, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Edelson, Nathan, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Epps, Dick, 1969 (Box 24, Folder 12)
- Esmara, Hendra (Box 24, Folder 13)
- Farhi, Andre 1, 1969-1971 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- Farhi, Andre (2), 1969 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Fu-Chen, Lo, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 16)
- Fujita, Masahisa, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 17)
- Glickman, Norman, 1964-1967 (Box 24, Folder 18)
- Hong, Sung Woong, 1971-1972 (Box 24, Folder 19)
- Gordon, Peter (1), 1971 (Box 24, Folder 20)
- Gordon, Peter (2) (Box 24, Folder 21)
- Jones, Peter R (Box 24, Folder 22)
- Hammer, Thomas R. (Box 24, Folder 23)
- Kawashima, Tatsuhiko, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 24)
- Kissin, John, 1966-1970 (Box 24, Folder 25)
- Kombatkokne, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 26a)
- Kwiatkowski, 1968-1970 (Box 24, Folder 26b)
- Lange, Jan (Box 24, Folder 26c)
- Langford, Thomas W, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 27)
- Illinois Population Projections, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 28)
- McDaniel, Bob, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 29)
- Menchik, Mark D, 1969-1972 (Box 24, Folder 30)
- Miller, Ted, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 31)
- Mudge, Richard R., 1971 (Box 24, Folder 32)
- Robinson, Frank (Box 24, Folder 33)
- Platt, Jeffrey, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 34a)
- Bruno Riendeau, 1969 (Box 24, Folder 34b)
- Robinson, Frank, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 34c)
- Romanoff, Eli, 1966-1970 (Box 24, Folder 34d)
- Salama, Ovadia, 1970-1971 (Box 24, Folder 35)
- Slater, Paul B, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 36)
- Silvers, Arthur, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 37)
- Smith, Tony E, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 38)
- Mumphrey, Tony, 1972-1973 (Box 24, Folder 39)
- Okabe, Atsuyuki (Box 24, Folder 40)
- Tappata, Heber N, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 41)
- Tolosa, Hamilton C, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 42)
- Williams, Dan, 1969 (Box 24, Folder 43a)
- Yamashita (Box 24, Folder 43b)
- Zerdy, Edward (Box 24, Folder 43c)
- Zuker, Richard C, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 43d)
- Sources of Potential Students, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 44)
- ARA Dept. of Defense materials 1961-62, 1961-1962 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  Area Redevelopment Administration
- ARA Dept of Defense Materials 1961-62, 1961-1962 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Isard/Dacey 1960s (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Crossed Out 1 and otherwise unmarked material 1960-61, 1960-1961 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Crossed Out 2 and otherwise unmarked material 1960-61, 1960-1961 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Crossed Out 3 (A)and otherwise unmarked material 1960-61, 1960-1961 (Box 25, Folder 6A)
- Crossed Out 3 (B)and otherwise unmarked material 1960-61, 1960-1961 (Box 25, Folder 6B)
- Crossed Out 3 (B)and otherwise unmarked material 1960-61, 1960-1961 (Box 25, Folder 6C)
- Crossed Out (General theory book c. 1969)--1, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Crossed Out--General Theory (2)--Ch.3 materials, Written in the 1960s (with Tung) published 1969, 1960s (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Crossed Out--General Theory Book materials, c. 1969 (3), 1960s (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Crossed Out--General Theory Book materials, c. 1969 (4), 1960s (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Crossed Out--General Theory Book materials, c. 1969, 1960s (Box 25, Folder 11)
- Report on Metropolitan Problems (for Ford Foundation 1955), 1955 (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Michigan Project 1950's & 60s--1, 1955-1962 (Box 25, Folder 13)
- Michigan Project 1950's & 60s--2, 1953-1956 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- University Training Program for Research, Planning, and Other Personnel, 1955 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- The Ford Foundation and Problems of Business & Economics (Harkavy, Oscar--post 1951), 1961 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- The Metropolitan Study Group--Summer 1955, 1954-1955 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Report of the Metropolitan Study Group 1955 (2), 1955 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Community Education--Howard, JT 1955, 1955 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Working Paper for the Ford Foundation's Advisory Committee on a Program in Metropolitan Area Problems and Studies-- Woodbury, Coleman (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Reports & Drafts, 1955 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Notes--1939, 1939 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Notebook on Theory (Box 26, Folder 9)
- WI's Noteson Palander- 1945, 1945 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- WI's Notes on Dean's The Theory of the Graphic Location of Economic Activities, 1938 (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Reading Notes 1 (Box 26, Folder 12)
- Reading Notes 2 (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Reading Notes 3 (Box 26, Folder 14)
- RSA Conference 1954--Detroit, MI, 1954 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- RSA Detroit Conference 1954 Correspondence--May-June 1954, 1954 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- RSA Detroit Conference 1954 Correspondence--July-Aug 1954, 1954 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- RSA Detroit Conference 1954 Correspondence--September 1954, 1954 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- RSA Detroit Conference 1954 Correspondence--October 1954, 1954 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- RSA Detroit Conference 1954 Correspondence--November 1954, 1954 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- RSA Detroit Conference 1954 Correspondence--December 1954- January 1955, 1954-1955 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- RSA Detroit Conference 1954 Correspondence--Misc. Correspondence, 1954 (Box 27, Folder 8)
- NICB Atomic Energy Conference--July 1953, 1953 (Box 27, Folder 9)
- Western Regional Economist meetings, AIP--June 25-27, 1953, 1953 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  American Institute of Planners and Western Regional Economist meetings
- AAG Meetings--March 1953, 1953 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  Association of American Geographers
- AEA Meeting; Professor Innis Correspondence, Dec. 1952, 1952 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  American Economic Association conference
- Econometric Society Meetings, Correspondence w/Robert Strotz, 1952 (Box 27, Folder 13)
- Newsletter to Regional Researchers--February 23, 1953, Perloff's Paper, 1953 (Box 27, Folder 14)
- Newsletter to Regional Researchers--April 23, 1953 Ackerman's Paper, 1953 (Box 27, Folder 15)
- Newsletter to Regional Researchers:--June 9, 1953; Englebert's Paper & Hoover Comments, 1953 (Box 27, Folder 16)
- American Association for the Advancement of Science--Correspondence 1952, 1952 (Box 27, Folder 17)
- Misc. Regional Science Journals and Publications, 1956-79 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  Journals from Centro de Ciencia Regional, Papers of RSA Volume 42, 1979
- Ecologic-Economic Analysis for Regional Development by Isard et al., 1972 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  Book by Isard
- Steel (1), 1944-1954 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  Research
- Steel--Gulf Coast AMWs Estimates (2) (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Steel (3), 1948-1956 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Steel--(4) Industrial, 1950 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Steel (5) UN Economic & Social Council 1949, 1949 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Steel--(6), 1949-1952 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Steel--(7), 1948-1954 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Utah Economic and Business Reivew, Vol. 11, 1951 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Steel-- (8a) (Box 28, Folder 9)
- Steel--(8b) Some Locational Factors in the Iron and Steel Industry... (Box 28, Folder 10)
- Steel--(8c), 1950 (Box 28, Folder 11)
- Steel--(8d) (Box 28, Folder 12)
- Steel--(8e) (Box 28, Folder 13)
- Steel--(9) (Box 28, Folder 14)
- Steel--(10) (Box 28, Folder 15)
- Steel--(11), 1949-1950 (Box 28, Folder 19)
- Steel--(12), 1949 (Box 28, Folder 17)
- Steel--(13), 1953 (Box 28, Folder 18)
- RSA Memberships and Newsletter--Sept. 20, 1955, 1956 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Dec. 12, 1955--Letter Regarding RSA Conference Dec. 27, 1955: "Regional Science--Nature and Scope", 1955 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- July 28, 1955; Newsletter, 1955 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- March 14. 1955--Newsletter RSA Regarding Business Meeting in Detroit, 1955 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Correspondence RSA 1956 Cleveland--A to K, 1956 (Box 29, Folder 5)